[{"id":0,"question":"6/1","choices":[5,6,7],"rightAnswer":6,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":1,"question":"9/9","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"question":"3-0","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":3,"question":"1+2","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"question":"7-1","choices":[5,6,7],"rightAnswer":6,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":5,"question":"6/2","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":6,"question":"6-4","choices":[1,2,3],"rightAnswer":2,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":7,"question":"2-1","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":8,"question":"6/2","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":9,"question":"5*9","choices":[44,45,46],"rightAnswer":45,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":10,"question":"4-2","choices":[1,2,3],"rightAnswer":2,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":11,"question":"9/3","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":12,"question":"7-6","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":13,"question":"7*8","choices":[55,56,57],"rightAnswer":56,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":14,"question":"4/4","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":15,"question":"8/8","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":16,"question":"5/5","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":17,"question":"6-3","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":18,"question":"2+0","choices":[1,2,3],"rightAnswer":2,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":19,"question":"4+6","choices":[9,10,11],"rightAnswer":10,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":20,"question":"14+9","choices":[22,23,24],"rightAnswer":23,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":21,"question":"81-2","choices":[78,79,80],"rightAnswer":79,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":22,"question":"54/2","choices":[26,27,28],"rightAnswer":27,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":23,"question":"23*4","choices":[91,92,93],"rightAnswer":92,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":24,"question":"30*4","choices":[119,120,121],"rightAnswer":120,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":25,"question":"16-4","choices":[11,12,13],"rightAnswer":12,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":26,"question":"56/7","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":27,"question":"91/7","choices":[12,13,14],"rightAnswer":13,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":28,"question":"89*6","choices":[533,534,535],"rightAnswer":534,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":29,"question":"82+7","choices":[88,89,90],"rightAnswer":89,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":30,"question":"56*9","choices":[503,504,505],"rightAnswer":504,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":31,"question":"26-2","choices":[23,24,25],"rightAnswer":24,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":32,"question":"64/4","choices":[15,16,17],"rightAnswer":16,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":33,"question":"73*2","choices":[145,146,147],"rightAnswer":146,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":34,"question":"95+4","choices":[98,99,100],"rightAnswer":99,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":35,"question":"86+5","choices":[90,91,92],"rightAnswer":91,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":36,"question":"48/6","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":37,"question":"30+1","choices":[30,31,32],"rightAnswer":31,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":38,"question":"96/6","choices":[15,16,17],"rightAnswer":16,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":39,"question":"30-1","choices":[28,29,30],"rightAnswer":29,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":40,"question":"22*88","choices":[1935,1936,1937],"rightAnswer":1936,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":41,"question":"95-91","choices":[3,4,5],"rightAnswer":4,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":42,"question":"85+58","choices":[142,143,144],"rightAnswer":143,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":43,"question":"196/4","choices":[48,49,50],"rightAnswer":49,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":53,"question":"992/8","choices":[123,124,125],"rightAnswer":124,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":59,"question":"26*74","choices":[1923,1924,1925],"rightAnswer":1924,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":46,"question":"85-33","choices":[51,52,53],"rightAnswer":52,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":47,"question":"674/2","choices":[336,337,338],"rightAnswer":337,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":48,"question":"45+87","choices":[131,132,133],"rightAnswer":132,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":49,"question":"74*51","choices":[3773,3774,3775],"rightAnswer":3774,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":50,"question":"354/6","choices":[58,59,60],"rightAnswer":59,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":51,"question":"990/9","choices":[109,110,111],"rightAnswer":110,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":52,"question":"77-46","choices":[30,31,32],"rightAnswer":31,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":53,"question":"992/8","choices":[123,124,125],"rightAnswer":124,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":54,"question":"85+43","choices":[127,128,129],"rightAnswer":128,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":55,"question":"85+48","choices":[132,133,134],"rightAnswer":133,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":56,"question":"600/8","choices":[74,75,76],"rightAnswer":75,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":57,"question":"405/5","choices":[80,81,82],"rightAnswer":81,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":58,"question":"23+80","choices":[102,103,104],"rightAnswer":103,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":59,"question":"26*74","choices":[1923,1924,1925],"rightAnswer":1924,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":60,"question":"536+37","choices":[572,573,574],"rightAnswer":573,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":79,"question":"610*70","choices":[42699,42700,42701],"rightAnswer":42700,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":62,"question":"232/29","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":63,"question":"226-29","choices":[196,197,198],"rightAnswer":197,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":68,"question":"243+77","choices":[319,320,321],"rightAnswer":320,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":65,"question":"414/18","choices":[22,23,24],"rightAnswer":23,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":66,"question":"674*51","choices":[34373,34374,34375],"rightAnswer":34374,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":72,"question":"337+88","choices":[424,425,426],"rightAnswer":425,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":68,"question":"243+77","choices":[319,320,321],"rightAnswer":320,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":69,"question":"900/30","choices":[29,30,31],"rightAnswer":30,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":70,"question":"370*18","choices":[6659,6660,6661],"rightAnswer":6660,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":71,"question":"468*99","choices":[46331,46332,46333],"rightAnswer":46332,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":72,"question":"337+88","choices":[424,425,426],"rightAnswer":425,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":73,"question":"621+90","choices":[710,711,712],"rightAnswer":711,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":78,"question":"350/50","choices":[6,7,8],"rightAnswer":7,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":75,"question":"636/12","choices":[52,53,54],"rightAnswer":53,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":76,"question":"841-37","choices":[803,804,805],"rightAnswer":804,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":77,"question":"852-98","choices":[753,754,755],"rightAnswer":754,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":78,"question":"350/50","choices":[6,7,8],"rightAnswer":7,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":79,"question":"610*70","choices":[42699,42700,42701],"rightAnswer":42700,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":80,"question":"7866/18","choices":[436,437,438],"rightAnswer":437,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":81,"question":"173*438","choices":[75773,75774,75775],"rightAnswer":75774,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":82,"question":"666*204","choices":[135863,135864,135865],"rightAnswer":135864,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":83,"question":"8084/47","choices":[171,172,173],"rightAnswer":172,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":84,"question":"699+349","choices":[1047,1048,1049],"rightAnswer":1048,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":85,"question":"894+957","choices":[1850,1851,1852],"rightAnswer":1851,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":86,"question":"218+151","choices":[368,369,370],"rightAnswer":369,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":91,"question":"133+254","choices":[386,387,388],"rightAnswer":387,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":88,"question":"393+762","choices":[1154,1155,1156],"rightAnswer":1155,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":89,"question":"954-641","choices":[312,313,314],"rightAnswer":313,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":90,"question":"4180/19","choices":[219,220,221],"rightAnswer":220,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":91,"question":"133+254","choices":[386,387,388],"rightAnswer":387,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":95,"question":"385+290","choices":[674,675,676],"rightAnswer":675,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":93,"question":"954*197","choices":[187937,187938,187939],"rightAnswer":187938,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":94,"question":"365+675","choices":[1039,1040,1041],"rightAnswer":1040,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":95,"question":"385+290","choices":[674,675,676],"rightAnswer":675,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":96,"question":"227*758","choices":[172065,172066,172067],"rightAnswer":172066,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":97,"question":"645*556","choices":[358619,358620,358621],"rightAnswer":358620,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":98,"question":"684-382","choices":[301,302,303],"rightAnswer":302,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":99,"question":"382-348","choices":[33,34,35],"rightAnswer":34,"qOperator":"-","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false}]